Kamen Lion
No, we're going to watch Cats of Japan!
Stop that!
Are you fighting over the TV again?
Doraemon started it...
It's Nobita's fault...
STOP IT!
Honestly...
I'm going to cut that TV in half one of these days.
That's a good idea!
Dividing Blade
No, don't!
Ahh!
Hmm?
There's two of them!
Haha! This tool splits anything it cuts into two!
Wow!
Whoa! It really works!
It's a bit small, but...
Nobita, Shizuka chan is on the phone.
Huh?
Ah, Shizuka chan?
, sorry! I forgot!
be right there!
forgot that I promised to do homework with Shizuka!
You should get goingthen
But can't miss this episode of Masked Lion
Then you should stay
But if I break my promise, Shizuka chan will
be angry with me. What should I do?
You should make up your mind!
Of course!
Ajust need to become two people..
Good luck with that...
Hub?
I did it! It worked!
From the clothes to the sword, a perfect match!
I'll take care of the TV and leave the homework to you.
No nothink you should take care of the homework.
Hmm?
You little... Just who do you think you are?
Heyhey, hey!
You... what do you think you're doing?
NOBITA!
Draw straws!
Okay
This is unfair!
But, I'll be together with Shizuka chanThat's okay.I guess.
Hey Nobita!
You're playing baseball with us. Let's go
Uh, today can't... ...
What did you say?
Okayokay
I'll just split in half, and be right there.
It's a promise. Don't forget!
Iguess I don't have a choice
Wow!
Isplit again! Now I'm just a quarter the size.
Which of us has to go play baseball? Janken pon!
Darn!
This bag is so heavy... Oh oh oh!
I'll be there as soon as can! Shizuka is waiting!
better hurry.
Oh, Uncle Nobi?
That voice... Nobita-kun?
What happened to your glasses?
live switched to contacts.
But then I dropped them...
Please... Help me find them!
I don't have a choice.
fill leave half of myself here to help.
Ogh, soheavy...!
be there as soon as we find them!
I'm relying on you.
It's heading your way, Nobita!
Back! Back!
Ah, man...
Ugh, it's heavy!
NOBITA!
You're fired!
Phew, thank goodness!
Help me!
Pervert!
No no no... I didn't mean to do any thing...
I'm just having a really bad day...
! Wait! Hey, let me go! Hey!
Here it is!
What a relief!
Here you go.
Thanks! Let me get you a soda in return.
SorryI have to go!
hope that me who went to do homework is okay.
Huh?
Hey!
Help me!
What are you doing up there?
Just get me down from here quick!
UghI hate climbing trees.
I'm going to fall! Help me!
Stop flailing!
Ahhhhh!!!!
We better hurry! Shizuka's not going to be happy!
One-two! One-two!
Don't miss next week's episode of Masked Lion"!
Phewthat was amusing!
Hey put me and my half back together.
will once this show is over.
Alright, Shizukachan's been waiting!
Shizukachan!
Hube
Beright there!
Aren't you late?
What were you doing?
thought some help would make the work go faster.
Oh.
No no, that's not right.
Huh?
No, that's not it at all!
Yeah, that's it!
No no no!
told you that's wrongThat's not the answer!
Nodefinitely right!
being so stubborn!
What!?
Shut up! Why should I trust you?
told you, you're wrong!
I'm right!
NoI'm right!
Why are you fighting with yourself? Stop it!!
Oh, boy...
Hmm?
Nobita-kun
Napping, again?
NOBITA!
Nobita-kun?
What's wrong? Get up!
Doraemon? You've been such a good friend...
What happened?
It's over for me...
Mama's ring, grandma's heirloom...
Shizukachan will be surprised to see this!
NOBITA!
Oh!
Hey! Wait!
I've been so worried, haven't been able to concentrate in class.
You're never able to concentrate.
definitely get a zero on the test tomorrow.
Oh huh.
Mama will scold me, and lose all interest in studying.
My grades will plummet, and never finish elementary school!
That's awfully pessimistic.
In that case, why don't you try this out?
Lost Object Recovery Machine
Okay
Picture in your mind the ring you lost.
As clearly as you can.
RingRingMama's ring!
Then, you just turn this dial...
Oh!
Wow! That's it!
Alright! I'm saved!
Okay now you can study.
Hold on, wait!
Does that machine work on any thing?
Yeah, if you remember the shape...
but you really should be studying.
First, I have some things I want back!
Amazing!
That given up on youonly to have you return! It's like a dream!
Alrightfill go for a thousand yen, next.
A thousand yen. A thousand yen.
Hey, it's not coming out.
When did you lose it?
I didn't really lose it...
it okay it just spent it?
Stop this, and get studying!!
Don't get so angry.
With this brain, it doesn't really matter if I study or not
What, what did you say?
I'm through with this!
Grrr...
I wonder if there's anything else live lost?
Ah, of course!
It's gone! My ring is gone!
Where, where is it?
That's terrible! I can't believe you lost mother's heirloom
What, what can I do?
Where did it gol?
Mama, are you looking for something?
No no, there's nothing wrong
My wallet!
lost my wallet!
Your wallet? That's no good. Wait here a sec.
What should do?
Ha ha! All the manga Mama threw away!
This too?
Oh, right hid this in one of the manga
Oh.
Wait! I'm still using that!
Focus on the thing you lost, and it'll come back to you.
Thank you! I'll try it out right now.
Huh?
RingRingRing
Hub?
It really worked!
The ringis gone!
Hey, Nobita-kun!
Doraemon, please give me back that machine.
promise I'll only use it one more time.
Do you promise you'll study right after?
I do. I do.
Okay, I'll give you ten minutes.
Thank you!
Grandma, I won't lose this again.
RingRing
There it is!
It's gone. The ring is gone!
How could that happen?
Thank goodness!
Okay, now get back all the toys live ever lost.
Where could I have dropped it?
Oh!
You don't happen to be looking for a ringdo you?
How do you know that?
We saw it, didn't we?
Nobita lost an expensivelooking ring around here.
Hub?
He didn't tell you?
We probably shouldn't have told you that. Hahaha!
Nobi-chan!
That's...
Ah, Mrs. Nobi.
Ah, SenseiHow are you today?
Actuallythis is good timing
Something about my son?
Nobi kun was inattentive all day long today...
haven't used this since kindergarten.
Everyone called me "baby" and laughed at me.
The taste of rubber brings back memories.
Things were good back then.
No one ever hounded me to study.
Nobita, it's been twenty minutes...
Everyday, all had to do was play, eat, and sleep.
Hey, how old are you?
you have so much time to think about the past...
You should spend more time thinking about the future!
The future?
There's nothing good in my future...
I'm stupid, and I fail at whatever I do.
The only time I was happy was when my grandma was alive...
Nobita!
Mama!
just met with your teacher
He told me you were screwing around all class!
I have a reason for that...
don't want to hear any excuses.
It's nothing but excuses from you.
That's...
That's because you always get mad at me.
Is that why you didn't tell me about the ring?
Huh?
I'm disappointed with you.
Anywayyour lack of motivation is the
reason you always get into trouble.
What would grandma say if she saw you now?
If grandma were alive, she'd tell you not to nag me so much.
What?
After all, I'm...
I'm just a worthless human being!
Get out of my way!
Grandma.
Ireally want to go back to that time...
Oh, did you really do it againNobi chan?
It's okay
It's just a little mistake
Nobi-chan you've really gotten big!
What an interesting pattern you've made!
It's okay.
cast a charm...
to make sure there are no leaks tonight, okay?
She was so nice.
Grandma.
miss grandma.
Huh?
That daruma...
Nobichan it's okay now
Grandma!
It's okay. It's okay. It was scary, wasn't it?
Here's a charm to protect you.
A daruma?
That's right.
It was after I got this daruma. Grandma!
Nobi-chan, why don't you play outside today?
No, I want to play here with you, grandma!
Your grandma will be alright.
Look, Nobichan look outside.
Ah!
Oh, it's snowing!
Isn't it pretty? Go take a look.
Okay.
Look, the daruma has already gotten back up.
Nobichan you should get up too.
Grandma, you should be in bed!
It's okay
can't sleep if hear my Nobichan crying
I'm sorry, grandma.
Lie down grandma.
Thank youThe daruma is pretty great, isn't heNobi-chan?
Why?
No matter how many times he falls over he can always get up on his own.
Uh huh.
I'd love to see you become like the daruma,
Nobi-chan. It will make me happy
No matter how many times you fallyou'll be able to get up again.
I'd have no worries if you were that way
I'll become a daruma. I promise!
Really?
You're such a good child
Grandma.
Oh myI went too far.
But grandma did tell me often...
Scold whatever needs scolding.
Anyone can just say those kind things...
any time.
I see.
I should probably talk with him again, though.
Mama.
Nobi-chan.
I'm sorry
Grandma, don't worry.
From here on, I may fall many times more...
but I'll definitely get up on my own. Watch over me!
Grandma